PIERRE-LOUIS DELCROIX

Passionated student of computer science since 2016 with multiple work experiences through freelance. Looking for a 6 months internship during the second semester 2022 where I can bring my coding and software engineering expertise in a seasoned IT team.



CONTACT

pierrelouisdelcroix@gmail.com

**** +33 6 36 10 39 78

https://pierrelouisdelx.github.io

@Pierrelouisdelx

in Pierre-Louis Delcroix

HARD SKILLS

Programming C C# C++ Python HTML/CSS Javascript PHP SQL Operating Systems Linux

Software & Tools

Windows

Blender
ArduPilot
Unity
Git
NodeJs

Languages
French - native
English
Spanish

SOFT SKILLS

Motivated Creative Organised

Determined Self-learning Curious

Team Working



WORK HISTORY

09/2021 - Present

Paris, France

Web developper freelance

In parallel of my studies I am working as a freelance on malt.fr

1 07/2021 - 08/2021

• Le lavandou, France Waiter

For the purpose of my worker internship I was a waiter for one month in a French gastronomical restaurant

₩ June 2017

Work Experience at Advizzo, London Student

Advizzo is an IT startup combining behavioural science with data science in order to reduce water and energy consumption

EDUCATION

6 09/2019 - 07/2024

• Epita - 3rd year Student

Epita a school of engineering and computer science in which I have done multiple projects such as a POSIX shell, an optical character recognition software and a backend API in Java

1 09/2015 - 07/2019

• Lycee International de Londres Winston Churchill, London

High School Student

AWARDS

- Baccalaureat, June 2019
- **▼** Swimming competition 4 medals, June 2015, London
- ▼ International ski competition (bronze), 2007 Yong-Pyong, South Korea

EXPERIENCE

International:

- Erasmus in Riga Technical University, Latvia (January 2021 June 2021)
 Subjects: Database Management Systems, Software Engineering
- 2. London, England (2015 2019)
- 3. Asia (2007 2011): Seoul, Hong-Kong, Tokyo

Scouts: I have been involved into scouts since 2012 and I am currently a scout leader.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Drone: I am currently building my own autonomous drone using ardupilot and medianine

ProjectMagna: I am currently part of a team developing a video game under unity

INTERESTS

Electronics: Arduino

Sports: Taekwondo, Slackline, Alpinism, Ski

Computing: Computer vision, 3D Modeling, Cybersecurity